Huh
Love yours
Huh, love yours
No such thing
No such thing as a life
that's better than yours
that's better than yours (Love yours)
No such thing as a life
that's better than yours
No such thing, no such thing
Heart beatin' fast,
let a nigga know that he alive
Fake niggas, mad snakes
Snakes in the grass
let a nigga know that he arrived
Don't be sleepin' on your level
'Cause it's beauty in the struggle, nigga
(Beauty, beauty)
Goes for all y'all
It's beauty in the struggle, nigga
(Beauty, beauty)
Let me explain, yeah
It's beauty in the struggle,
ugliness in the success
Hear my words or listen
to my signal of distress
I grew up in the city,
and though sometimes we had less
Compared to some of my niggas
down the block, man, we were blessed
And life can't be no fairytale,
no once upon a time
But I be goddamned
if a nigga don't be tryin'
So tell me, Momma, please,
why you be drinkin' all the time?
Does all the pain he brought you
still linger in your mind?
'Cause pain still lingers on mine
On the road to riches,
listen, this is what you'll find
The good news is, nigga,
you came a long way
The bad news is, nigga, you went the wrong way
Think being broke was better
No such thing as a life
that's better than yours (Ha)
No such thing as a life that's better than yours
(Think being broke was better)
(Think being broke was better, yeah)
No such thing, no such thing
For what's money without happiness?
Or hard times without
the people you love?
Though I'm not sure
what's 'bout to happen next
I asked for strength
from the Lord up above
'Cause I been strong so far,
but I can feel my grip loosenin'
Quick, do somethin' before you lose it for good
Get it back and use it for good
And touch the people
how you did like before
I'm tired of livin' with demons
'cause they always invitin' more
Think being broke was better,
now I don't mean that phrase with no disrespect
To all my niggas out there livin' in debt
Cashin' minimal checks,
turn on the TV, see a nigga Rolex
And fantasize about a life with no stress
I mean this shit sincerely,
and as a nigga who was once in your shoes
Livin' with nothin' to lose,
I hope one day you hear me
Always gon' be a bigger house somewhere,
but nigga, feel me
Long as the people in that motherfucker
love you dearly
Always gon' be a whip
that's better than the one you got
Always gon' be some clothes
that's fresher than the ones you rock
Always gon' be a bitch
that's badder out there on the tours
But you ain't never gon' be happy
'til you love yours
No such thing as a life
that's better than yours (Love yours)
No such thing, no such thing
Heart beatin' fast,
let a nigga know that he alive
Fake niggas, mad snakes
Snakes in the grass
let a nigga know that he arrived